# Moog S. Leem

# UX Designer & Engineer

## Summary

I was born in Dec, 1991 in Seoul, South Korea.

Now(2018.03), I am a bachelor candidate of Mechanical Engineering and Information Science & Culture of Seoul National University
I am deeply interested in designing interaction system between human and technology (machine, computer, robot, etc.) especially focused on user experience, and in love with Hip-hop / RnB music.

# Work Experience

#### **ZUNGLE** Seoul, South Korea.

#### **R&D Team Intern**

**ZUNGLE** is a manufacturer of wearable BT device. As an R&D team Intern, i was involved in not only a hardware and a software development process but also a UX design process.

Supporting hardware development process, I could learn how to design embedded system from the very entry level. And also, because I was deeply involved in UX design process, I could learn the importance of understanding user's need and user experience before starting to develop the product, especially in making a wearable device.

Besides, I could learn the organic connection between the design, materials and manufacturing process.

2017.07 ~ 2017.12

# Special Experience

KATUSA Seoul, South Korea.

#### Discharged

I served my military service as a KATUSA. This experience was very special to me. I could improve my english skill dramatically during this period.

2011.12 ~ 2013.09

404WAREHOUSE Seoul, South Korea.

#### Member

404Warehouse is a multidisciplinary study group based in Seoul, South Korea.

This group is deeply interested in studying and experimenting new technologies to see the possibilities of these technologies' contribution to our daily lives.

So, 404Warehouse try to visualize new technologies in comprehensive ways for everybody.

As a member of this group, I managed media art project, interactive media project and a drone project.

2014 ~ Present

CRE8S of SNU Seoul, South Korea

#### Member

Cre8s is a media art group of non-art major students. As a member of this group, I was involved in interactive music & performance project as a producer and a developer. I designed total interactive performing system which interacts with movements of the dancers and a music lively.

2016.03 ~ 2016.12

### Education

SEOUL NATIONAL UNIVERSITY Seoul, South Korea

#### **BACHELOR CANDIDATE**

I am majoring Mechanical Engineering and also Information Science & Culture. I'm deeply interested in IoT system design and interaction system design especially focused on user experience.

2010.03 ~ 2018.08

INRoL of SNU Seoul, South Korea

#### **BACHELOR THESIS STUDENT**

2016.03 ~ 2017.03

As a senior student, I wrote my bachelor's thesis in INRoL (Interactive & Networked Robotics Laboratory). My thesis is about designing tele-operated interface system focused on usability.

I developed head-tracking stereo-camera module and attached it to mobile robot. User could tele-operate this mobile robot while sharing the camera vision using HMD. As writing this thesis, I could learn about the method of user centered design and the importance of ergonomic factors in designing human-robot interface.

ISC of SNU Seoul, South Korea

#### STUDENT RESEARCH INTERN

2018.03 ~ Ongoing

To understand UX design method and Interaction design further, i participated in student research intern program, especailly in HCI field under a teaching of prof. Hwajung Hong.

Skills

# Languages



# **Awards**

# Social

- Design, Manufacturing Process and Laboratory
- 1st Prize, 2016, Seoul National University

in linkedin.com/in/moogfromseoul